# **EDUARD PREDESCU**

eduard.florin.predescu@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardpredescu/ • https://github.com/epr3

### **SUMMARY**

I have six years of experience working with front end technologies including but not limited to: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Vue.js (2+3), React + any state management, Nuxt/Next.js, Tailwind/UnoCSS). I am proficient in React and Vue for front end, Go/Node.js for back end if it is required. I have some experience with mobile apps using React Native.

#### **EDUCATION**

### M.S., Economic Informatics

Graduated June 2019

Bucharest University of Economic Studies, Bucharest, RO

10

### Bachelor's degree, Economic Cybernetics

Graduated June 2017

Bucharest University of Economic Studies, Bucharest, RO

10

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Front End: React, Nuxt 2/3, Next.js, Vue 2/3, Tailwind, UnoCSS, Typescript, Svelte, Astro, HTML5, CSS3

Back End: Go, Node.js, Fiber, Postgres, MySQL/MariaDB, Storyblok, Prismic

DevOps: AWS, Gitlab CI, Netlify, Docker

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Cognizant Softvision, Bucharest, RO (Hybrid): Software Engineer

June 2020 - Present

- Maintain and develop microsites/event pages for client marketing website
- · Optimize and tweak Nuxt and Netlify for faster build times for client marketing website
- · Handled ETL operations for migration from Prismic CMS to Storyblok CMS for client marketing website
- Refactor UI to atomic design for marketing website
- · Handle serverless functions in Netlify for client marketing website
- · Maintain Postgres DB for CSR App
- Develop, refactor, architect backend API in Golang (w/ Echo, later w/ Fiber) for CSR App
- Manage docs and OpenAPI 3 definitions for CSR App
- Implement testing for CSR App
- Handle basic DevOps in Gitlab CI and AWS for CSR App

### Team Extension, Bucharest, RO: Front End Developer

Oct 2017 - Jun 2020

- Conducted technical interviews for front end recruitment
- Maintaining and expanding a 3D design dashboard using Vue.js, three.js and Laravel and elaborating a daily status report for the progress
- Implementing a mobile internal app using React Native for recruitment
- · Maintaining and expanding a social media aggregator app based on user generated content using Vue.js
- Creating a marketing website using Vue.js and Laravel Blade Templates for a large music company
- · Helping other coworkers on front end related queries

### Elsaco Solutions, Bucharest, RO: Software Developer

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017

- Maintained the company's presentation website in Wordpress
- Created a web scraper in Node.js for seeding a database for a discount management app prototype

### Eau de Web, Bucharest, RO: Front End Intern

May 2016 - Sep 2016

- Maintained http://junio.ro front end using Bootstrap, jQuery
- Maintained and expanded a marketing website using Jekyll, Bootstrap, JavaScript
- Added features for a reporting dashboard using Bootstrap and JavaScript

### **VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE**

# IT Member @ SiSC - Sindicatul Studenților din Cibernetică Nov 2015 – Jul 2019

Managed various public facing websites for events organised by the association.

## Front End Division Lead @ SiSC - Sindicatul Studenților din Cibernetică Jun 2016 - May 2017

Mentored new front end members and provided support on various technical challenges.

# Front End Padawan @ DevAcademy Nov 2016 - May 2017

Graduated from course and got up-to-date with front end technologies, especially Vue.js.

### **AWARDS**

### Winning Team @ Hackaton4Health 2019

https://www.startupcafe.ro/idei-si-antreprenori/liceeni-aplicatie-medicala-concurs.htm

• Developed an AR solution for surgery guidance as part of the winning team.